Shall ! get you a glass?
Oh, no. No, I'm tired.
Baby shower was rubbish.
I'm just going to go to bed.
Are you OK? Yeah. Yeah, I'm fine.
All right. Well, don't stay up
too late. You've got a lot to do.
l won't. Night-night.
Night, Stace.
Tim.
It's me again.
Keep hoping you'll pick up.
Call me back. I...
We need to talk...
.. properly about what happened.
SHE SOBS
What? No, I'm fine, honestly.
I'm just... I'm tired
and I've got my scan.
No, it's fine.
It's nothing to worry about.
You sure there's nothing else?
TI Like what?
Look, I know you don't want
to talk about the father,
and that's your choice,
but 1 am one of the people
that's not going to judge you.
I know.
And I do, I appreciate everything
that you've done. It's just...
I just can't talk about it.
Stop worrying, sweetheart.
I told you, you'll have
the money by the morning.
You know, it's just the bank
playing up this end. That's all.
Yes, don't worry.
Yeah. I love you, too.
Let's speak tomorrow, OK? Bye.
Er, Babe's finishing up downstairs.
We're all done. Sweet.
Did you sort that money out?
Yeah. Yeah, all sorted.
I'll say goodnight, then.
Goodnight, son.
Mum! Libby! I'm so sorry I'm late.
Have I missed the baby shower?
No, no, it finished early.
Oh, that's such a shame!
So, you're planning on staying
a few nights, then?
I'm not going to risk
missing the birth!
I'm going to be right there
beside you holding your hand.
Denise - she's supposed
WW) to be a mate. [7
Some prat has got her up the duff
TW) and left her to it,
and she won't tell me who it is
YI) so I can sort it. [I
It was a one-night stand,
weren't it? No,
No, ! don't believe that.
It's got to be someone round here.
That's why she's keeping schtum.
What's the matter, Mick?
Buster.
Before he left, he was having
an affair with someone.
Now, ! don't know who it was,
and ! should've told you
and I'm sorry, OK?
Go on.
I was speaking to Denise earlier...
..and I mentioned Buster
and she went all weird.
So, what if he was having
an affair with her?
What if he's the father of her baby?
Body of a young woman's
just been found,
on the beach of the Malbonne estate.
! know this is a difficult time,
but I need to ask a few questions.
Can you open up, please?
What were you and her arguing about?
1 had nothing to do with her death.
Strange, isn't it?
Doesn't quite make sense.
Mo Farah - gold again!
Wimbledon champion...
STARTING PISTOL, WHISTLE
CHEERING
Costa...
That's a huge jump!
Great tackle...
And Bolt gets it!
Magnificent.
CHEERING
Mo Farah - gold again!
Wimbledon champion...
CHEERING CONTINUES
Sport in 2017 across the BBC.
Every choice you've ever made,
every path you've ever taken,
the man you are today is
your memory of Eurus.
! know this is difficult,
but you've got to keep it together.
Sherlock concludes...
A team of spy creatures
is on a mission
to uncover the secret lives
of wild animals.
Their hidden cameras capture
extraordinary behaviour.
What they reveal will surprise,
amaze, and make you smile.
Maybe they're more like us
than we ever thought possible.
On Panorama
On Panorama tonight:
On Panorama tonight: We
On Panorama tonight: We return
On Panorama tonight: We return to
Tunisia
Tunisia to
Tunisia to investigate
Tunisia to investigate the
Tunisia to investigate the terror
attack
attack on
attack on the
attack on the beach.
attack on the beach. I
attack on the beach. ! was
attack on the beach. ! was on
attack on the beach. I was on my
knees.
knees. I
knees. I just
knees. I just kept
knees. I just kept praying
knees. I just kept praying to
knees. I just kept praying to God
knees. I just kept praying to God to
keep
keep us
keep us alive.
keep us alive. We
keep us alive. We find
keep us alive. We find the
holidaymakers
holidaymakers who
holidaymakers who say
holidaymakers who say they
holidaymakers who say they were
misled
misled about
misled about the
misled about the risks.
misled about the risks. !
misled about the risks. 1 was
misled about the risks. 1 was just
constantly
constantly asking
constantly asking the
constantly asking the question
constantly asking the question -
constantly asking the question - are
we
we going
we going to
we going to be
we going to be safe?
we going to be safe? We
we going to be safe? We expose
we going to be safe? We expose the
police
police failures
police failures that
police failures that may
police failures that may have
police failures that may have cost
lives.
lives. The
lives. The policeman
lives. The policeman admitted
lives. The policeman admitted he
lives. The policeman admitted he was
so
so scared
so scared he
so scared he fainted.
so scared he fainted. And
so scared he fainted. And we
identify
identify the
identify the man
identify the man accused
identify the man accused of
Masterminding
Masterminding the
Masterminding the attack.
Masterminding the attack. I've
Masterminding the attack. I've not
seen
seen that,
seen that, if
seen that, if that's
seen that, if that's right
seen that, if that's right and
seen that, if that's right and the
families
families see
families see that,
families see that, they'll
families see that, they'll be
shocked)
shocked to
shocked to see
shocked to see the
shocked to see the face
shocked to see the face of
shocked to see the face of the
shocked to see the face of the man
that
that caused
that caused them
that caused them such
that caused them such terrible
sadness.
sadness. As
sadness. As the
sadness. As the inquests
sadness. As the inquests into
sadness. As the inquests into the
deaths
deaths of
deaths of 30
deaths of 30 British
deaths of 30 British tourists
prepare
prepare to
prepare to open,
prepare to open, we
prepare to open, we ask
prepare to open, we ask whether
people
people could
people could have
people could have been
people could have been saved.
This
This stretch
This stretch of
This stretch of the
This stretch of the beach
This stretch of the beach at
This stretch of the beach at Souse
in Tunisia
in Tunisia is
in Tunisia is now
in Tunisia is now abandoned.
in Tunisia is now abandoned. It
in Tunisia is now abandoned. It used
to
to be
to be packed
to be packed with
to be packed with British
to be packed with British tourists.
On
On June
On June 26,
On June 26, 2015,
On June 26, 2015, around
On June 26, 2015, around 11.
On June 26, 2015, around 11. 30am,
On June 26, 2015, around 11. 30am, a
man
man dressed
man dressed in
man dressed in black
man dressed in black walked
man dressed in black walked up
man dressed in black walked up the
beach.
beach. He
beach. He was
beach. He was carrying
beach. He was carrying an
beach. He was carrying an assault
rifle.
rifle. Everything
rifle. Everything seemed
rifle. Everything seemed to
rifle. Everything seemed to go
rifle. Everything seemed to go in
slow
slow motion.
slow motion. As
slow motion. As I
slow motion. As I looked
slow motion. As ! looked across,
slow motion. As I looked across,
there
there was
there was a
there was a man
there was a man standing
there was a man standing there
there was a man standing there with
a
a gun.
a gun. His
a gun. His eyes
a gun. His eyes made
a gun. His eyes made contact
a gun. His eyes made contact with
mine.
mine. The
mine. The gunman
mine. The gunman opened
mine. The gunman opened fire
mine. The gunman opened fire on
holidaymakers
holidaymakers sun
holidaymakers sun bathing
holidaymakers sun bathing in
holidaymakers sun bathing in front
of
of the Imperial
of the Imperial Hotel.
of the Imperial Hotel. It
of the Imperial Hotel. It was
captured
captured on
captured ona
captured on a mobile
captured on a mobile phone.
GUNFIRE
The
The gunfire
The gunfire was
The gunfire was just
The gunfire was just so
The gunfire was just so loud
The gunfire was just so loud and
rapid.
rapid. It
rapid. It was
rapid. It was all
rapid. It was all around
rapid. It was all around us,
rapid. It was all around us, the
explosions.
explosions. It
explosions. It was
explosions. It was as
explosions. It was as if
explosions. It was as if you
explosions. It was as if you were
explosions. It was as if you were in
the
the middle
the middle of
the middle of a
the middle of a war
the middle of a war zone.
the middle of a war zone. All
the middle of a war zone. All !
the middle of a war zone. All! kept
hearing
hearing was
hearing was people
hearing was people screaming
hearing was people screaming and
shouting.
shouting. It
shouting. It was
shouting. It was like
shouting. It was like mass
shouting. It was like mass panic.
Inside
Inside the
Inside the hotel,
Inside the hotel, the
Inside the hotel, the gunman
Inside the hotel, the gunman hunted
people
people down
people down in
people down in the
people down in the corridors.
people down in the corridors. She
said,
said, "I
said, "I can't
said, "I can't run
said, "I can't run no."
said, "I can't run no." I
said, "I can't run no." I said,
said, "I can't run no." I said, "If
you
you don't
you don't run,
you don't run, I'm
you don't run, I'm not
you don't run, I'm not going
you don't run, I'm not going to
you don't run, I'm not going to see
you
you again."
you again." Some
you again." Some holidaymakers
you again." Some holidaymakers took
refuge
refuge in
refuge in nearby
refuge in nearby hotels.
refuge in nearby hotels. Others
refuge in nearby hotels. Others were
take
take anyone
take anyone by
take anyone by local
take anyone by local shop
take anyone by local shop keepers.
Meanwhile,
Meanwhile, inside
Meanwhile, inside the
Meanwhile, inside the Imperial,
people
people barricaded
people barricaded themselves
people barricaded themselves in
their
their rooms.
their rooms. !
their rooms. I was
their rooms. I was on
their rooms. I was on my
their rooms. I was on my knees.
their rooms. I was on my knees. !
just
just kept
just kept praying
just kept praying to
just kept praying to God
just kept praying to God to
just kept praying to God to keep
just kept praying to God to keep us
alive.
alive. We
alive. We didn't
alive. We didn't expect
alive. We didn't expect to
alive. We didn't expect to get
alive. We didn't expect to get out.
We
We really
We really didn't.
We really didn't. It
We really didn't. It was
We really didn't. It was brave
Tunisians
Tunisians on
Tunisians on the
Tunisians on the beach
Tunisians on the beach who
Tunisians on the beach who chased
the
the gunman,
the gunman, Seifeddine
the gunman, Seifeddine Rezgui.
the gunman, Seifeddine Rezgui. The
the gunman, Seifeddine Rezqui. The
security
security forces
security forces were
security forces were nowhere
security forces were nowhere to
security forces were nowhere to be
seen.
38 tourists
38 tourists were
38 tourists were killed,
38 tourists were killed, 30
38 tourists were killed, 30 of
38 tourists were killed, 30 of them
British.
British. The
British. The inquests
British. The inquests into
British. The inquests into their
deaths
deaths start
deaths start next
deaths start next week,
deaths start next week, but
deaths start next week, but we've
discovered
discovered shocking
discovered shocking information
about
about the
about the Sousse
about the Sousse attack.
about the Sousse attack. We've
about the Sousse attack. We've seen
statements
statements from
statements from police
statements from police officers
there
there on
there on the
there on the day,
there on the day, which
there on the day, which reveal
there on the day, which reveal an
extraordinary
extraordinary catalogue
extraordinary catalogue of
extraordinary catalogue of failures.
We've
We've pieced
We've pieced together
We've pieced together and
We've pieced together and retraced
the
the movements
the movements of
the movements of different
the movements of different police
units
units that
units that day.
units that day. That
units that day. That morning,
units that day. That morning, the
chief
chief of
chief of the
chief of the tourist
chief of the tourist police,
chief of the tourist police, the
chief of the tourist police, the man
responsible
responsible for
responsible for the
responsible for the safety
responsible for the safety of
holidaymakers
holidaymakers was
holidaymakers was here
holidaymakers was here at
holidaymakers was here at the
Hannibal
Hannibal round
Hannibal round about,
Hannibal round about, when
Hannibal round about, when he
received
received a
received a call.
received a call. The
received a call. The police
received a call. The police chief
was
was told
was told there
was told there was
was told there was gunfire
was told there was gunfire on
was told there was gunfire on the
beach.
beach. He
beach. He was
beach. He was just
beach. He was just five
beach. He was just five minutes
beach. He was just five minutes away
with
with his
with his men
with his men in
with his men in the
with his men in the car.
with his men in the car. They
with his men in the car. They had
two
two assault
two assault rifles
two assault rifles and
two assault rifles and bullet-proof
vests
vests in.
vests in. His
vests in. His statement
vests in. His statement the
vests in. His statement the police
chief
chief admits
chief admits he
chief admits he was
chief admits he was afraid.
chief admits he was afraid. Instead
of
of going
of going straight
of going straight to
of going straight to where
of going straight to where the
shooting
shooting was,
shooting was, the
shooting was, the police
shooting was, the police chief
decided
decided to
decided to carry
decided to carry on
decided to carry on down
decided to carry on down this
decided to carry on down this road
and
and to
and to go
and to go to
and to go to this
and to go to this police
and to go to this police station
over
over here,
over here, in
over here, ina
over here, in a desperate
over here, in a desperate search
over here, in a desperate search for
more
more weapons.
more weapons. There
more weapons. There was
more weapons. There was a
more weapons. There was a horse
more weapons. There was a horse back
patrol
patrol just
patrol just a
patrol just a mile-and-a-half
patrol just a mile-and-a-half along
the
the beach.
the beach. But
the beach. But they
the beach. But they didn't
the beach. But they didn't respond.
Their
Their excuse?
Their excuse? Their
Their excuse? Their pistols
Their excuse? Their pistols were
Their excuse? Their pistols were no
match
match for
match for the
match for the gunman's
match for the gunman's Kalashnikov.
Another
Another police
Another police patrol
Another police patrol on
Another police patrol on a
Another police patrol on a quad
Another police patrol on a quad bike
claimed
claimed to
claimed to have
claimed to have a
claimed to have a flat
claimed to have a flat tyre.
claimed to have a flat tyre. As
Rezgui
Rezgui moved
Rezgui moved into
Rezgui moved into the
Rezgui moved into the hotel,
Rezgui moved into the hotel, the
police
police chief
police chief was
police chief was still
police chief was still at
police chief was still at the
station.
station. Finally
station. Finally the
station. Finally the police
station. Finally the police chief
and
and his
and his men
and his men left
and his men left the
and his men left the station
and his men left the station and
made
made their
made their way
made their way down
made their way down to
made their way down to the
made their way down to the beach
towards
towards the
towards the hotels.
towards the hotels. Two
towards the hotels. Two other
towards the hotels. Two other police
officers
officers then
officers then arrived
officers then arrived by
officers then arrived by boat,
officers then arrived by boat, armed
with
with an
with an assault
with an assault rifle.
with an assault rifle. Their
admissions
admissions are
admissions are the
admissions are the most
admissions are the most shocking
admissions are the most shocking of
all.
all. One
all. One takes
all. One takes off
all. One takes off his
all. One takes off his police
all. One takes off his police shirt,
so
so he
so he won't
so he won't be
so he won't be shot.
so he won't be shot. The
so he won't be shot. The other
faints
faints out
faints out of
faints out of fear.
faints out of fear. When
faints out of fear. When the
faints out of fear. When the police
chief
chief and
chief and his
chief and his men
chief and his men finally
chief and his men finally arrived,
they
they wasted
they wasted more
they wasted more time
they wasted more time by
they wasted more time by going
they wasted more time by going to
the
the wrong
the wrong hotel.
the wrong hotel. From
the wrong hotel. From the
the wrong hotel. From the time
the wrong hotel. From the time that
Rezgui
Rezgui fired
Rezgui fired his
Rezgui fired his first
Rezgui fired his first shot,
Rezgui fired his first shot, it
Rezgui fired his first shot, it was
around
around 40
around 40 minutes
around 40 minutes before
around 40 minutes before he
around 40 minutes before he was
finally
finally killed
finally killed down
finally killed down this
finally killed down this road.
finally killed down this road. The
Tunisian
Tunisian authorities
Tunisian authorities concluded
Tunisian authorities concluded the
police
police had
police had no
police had no plan
police had no plan to
police had no plan to counter
police had no plan to counter a
terror
terror attack,
terror attack, they
terror attack, they weren't
professional
professional and
professional and didn't
professional and didn't do
professional and didn't do their
duty.
duty. If
duty. If they
duty. If they had,
duty. If they had, perhaps
duty. If they had, perhaps lives
could
could have
could have been
could have been saved.
We told
We told the
We told the lawyers
We told the lawyers representing
families
families at
families at the
families at the inquests
families at the inquests about
families at the inquests about these
revelations.
revelations. The
revelations. The police
revelations. The police response
revelations. The police response was
chaotic.
chaotic. They
chaotic. They didn't
chaotic. They didn't communicate
properly.
properly. They
properly. They were
properly. They were slow.
properly. They were slow. They
seemed
seemed to
seemed to be
seemed to be afraid
seemed to be afraid of
seemed to be afraid of confronting
the
the gunman.
the gunman. What
the gunman. What do
the gunman. What do you
the gunman. What do you think
the gunman. What do you think would
be
be the families
be the families response
be the families response to
be the families response to that?
They'll
They'll be
They'll be shocked
They'll be shocked to
They'll be shocked to hear
They'll be shocked to hear that.
They'll be shocked to hear that. The
families
families would
families would have
families would have been
families would have been affected
families would have been affected by
the
the time
the time it
the time it took
the time it took for
the time it took for the
the time it took for the police
the time it took for the police to
get
get to
get to the
get to the hotel.
get to the hotel. Some
get to the hotel. Some families
get to the hotel. Some families have
lost
lost two
lost two or
lost two or more
lost two or more members.
lost two or more members. They're
having
having therapy
having therapy for
having therapy for psychiatric
conditions.
conditions. Some
conditions. Some have
conditions. Some have financial
losses.
losses. They
losses. They lost
losses. They lost their
losses. They lost their main
losses. They lost their main bread
winner
winner and
winner and have
winner and have got
winner and have got real
winner and have got real money
worries.
worries. It's
worries. It's devastating
worries. It's devastating on
worries. It's devastating on all
concerned.
concerned. The
concerned. The attack
concerned. The attack shouldn't
concerned. The attack shouldn't have
come
come as
come asa
come asa surprise.
The Arab
The Arab Spring
The Arab Spring began
The Arab Spring began right
The Arab Spring began right here
The Arab Spring began right here in
Tunisia
Tunisia six
Tunisia six years
Tunisia six years ago.
Tunisia six years ago. The
dictatorship
dictatorship was
dictatorship was toppled.
dictatorship was toppled. The
dictatorship was toppled. The once
all-powerful
all-powerful security
all-powerful security forces
all-powerful security forces were
all-powerful security forces were in
disarray.
disarray. And
disarray. And it
disarray. And it wasn't
disarray. And it wasn't long
disarray. And it wasn't long before
Islamist
Islamist militants
Islamist militants gained
Islamist militants gained a
foothold.
foothold. Disillusioned
foothold. Disillusioned young
Tunisians
Tunisians have
Tunisians have since
Tunisians have since joined
Tunisians have since joined the
so-called
so-called Islamic
so-called Islamic State
so-called Islamic State in
so-called Islamic State in their
thousands.